

CHAD HOROHOE

SENIOR SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER SAN FRANCISCO, CA

OBJECTIVE

Building tools for small teams of engineers in a single location. Serving knowledge to hundreds of millions of users across the globe. Helping to put vaccines in the arms of hundreds of thousands of patients during a global pandemic. For well over a decade, I've helped organizations scale using the best tools at hand. Always curious, constantly striving to learn more and excel in my line of work.

SKILLS

Kubernetes, AWS, Debian/ Ubuntu, Docker, Terraform, Python, Git/ GitHub, Redis, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, MySQL, Java, Prometheus, Grafana

EXPERIENCE

SR. SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER • LUMA HEALTH • JANUARY 2020 – APRIL Migrated company infrastructure from third-party container hosting to in-house managed Kubernetes installation on AWS, at a cost savings of roughly 70% per month. Built out entirely new GitOps-driven CI/CD pipeline backed by Flux to accelerate deployments. Drove adoption of improvements to company security posture, notably: hardware security keys for admin users.

SR. SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER • ASAPP • JUNE 2018 – DECEMBER 2019 Implemented company-wide tagging policies for AWS resources for compliance and cost optimization. Provided ongoing infrastructure & architectural consultation for other teams. Transitioned 200+ engineers from individual IAM Users to shared IAM Roles per team. Provisioned all new and documented existing infrastructure as code via Terraform.

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER • WIKIMEDIA • JANUARY 2016 – JUNE 2018 Redesigned CI/CD pipeline, which orchestrated efficient large-scale production software deployments. Production support, including debugging and troubleshooting post-deployment issues.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • WIKIMEDIA • JUNE 2010 – JANUARY 2016Researched, designed and implemented scalable replacement for aging in-house full-text search engine. Reviewed PHP code across multiple subsystems, providing actionable feedback and learning opportunities for fellow engineers.

EDUCATION

B.S. MANAGEMENT & INFORMATION SYSTEMS • 2012 Virginia Commonwealth University, Richmond, VA





